<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Jake&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://jake-shadle.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Jake&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-EN</language>
    <copyright>(c) 2016 Jake Shadle.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 19:38:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jake-shadle.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Trying out this blogging thing</title>
      <link>https://jake-shadle.github.io/2016/09/28/trying-out-this-blogging-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 19:38:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jake-shadle.github.io/2016/09/28/trying-out-this-blogging-thing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Though I have enjoyed reading coding blogs for years now, I have never thought seriously about doing my own, most
probably because the main language I use is &lt;strong&gt;C++&lt;/strong&gt;, which doesn&amp;rsquo;t really inspire me, to say the least.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, I &lt;em&gt;have&lt;/em&gt; been inspired by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.rust-lang.org/en-US/&#34;&gt;Rust&lt;/a&gt; for about a year or so now (and still going
strong!). While it has been more than a year since &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.rust-lang.org/2015/05/15/Rust-1.0.html&#34;&gt;1.0&lt;/a&gt;, there is
a still a huge amount of stuff that is improving on a daily basis, and as
&lt;a href=&#34;http://mgattozzi.github.io/2016/09/27/blog-about-rust.html&#34;&gt;this blog post&lt;/a&gt; points out, Rust needs more content of all
types.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had a wonderful conversation with &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/steveklabnik&#34;&gt;Steve Klabnik&lt;/a&gt; and others about this a couple
months back when he came to Boston for the meetup. Someone had asked what one of the biggest blockades to adoption he
could see being in Rust’s way. His answer was that we need people to talk about Rust and provide tutorials and projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought maybe this blog could be one way I could help the Rust community. Not only because they are a lovely bunch of
people, but also because I want to increase that community to include more and more C++ programmers so that the balance
eventually tips over and they start using Rust as their default language of choice when starting new projects or rewriting
old ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also when I attended &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.rustfest.eu/&#34;&gt;RustFest&lt;/a&gt; I was struck by this quote from
&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/ag_dubs&#34;&gt;Ashley Williams&lt;/a&gt; in her &lt;a href=&#34;https://intermezzos.github.io/rustfest2016&#34;&gt;talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;teaching is nature&amp;rsquo;s way of letting you know how sloppy your thinking is&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is something I have thought about before, but it definitely reminded me that I absolutely learn a lot more when I
want to relay information to a wider audience (mostly to reduce my chances of looking like a dumbass).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So in conclusion, I guess I am writing this because I am selfish and want to use a nicer language when possible, as well
as improve myself, and my evil master plan is to write nice (and hopefully helpful) stuff about Rust. (I will try to
keep &lt;strong&gt;C++&lt;/strong&gt; snark to a minimum, but I have used the language for so long now, I think I deserve some leeway)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-rust&#34;&gt;fn main() {
    println!(&amp;quot;Hello, Internetz&amp;quot;);
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>